freemooviesonline.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Watch Free Movies Online

Category: [FMO](http://www.freemooviesonline.com/fmo.html)

FMO is committed to protecting your privacy when you use the FMO Service, which is comprised of (i) the FMO website, currently located at www.freemooviesonline.com (and/or any successor or additional website(s) owned or operated by or for FMO); (ii) the FMO syndication network (which includes third party websites); (iii) and/or any other technology and/or services that FMO provides its users. The following Privacy Policy was prepared to inform you of the information we collect about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information.

It is very important that you read and understand our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms set out in our Privacy Policy, please do not use the FMO Service.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will advise you that changes have been made by posting a notice on our website or otherwise. Your use of the FMO Service constitutes your acceptance of the terms of our Privacy Policy, as may be amended or revised by us, and you are advised to consult our Privacy Policy regularly for any changes (revisions will be reflected by the "last update" notation below).

If you have any questions regarding FMO's policies or practices relating to privacy, please direct them to [admin@freemooviesonline.com](mailto:admin@freemooviesonline.com).

This Privacy Policy was last updated on _March 12, 2009._

**Collection and Use of Information**

While using the FMO Service you may, among other things, gather information on our website, publish content and subscribe to one of our services. In doing so, we may collect certain information about you.

We may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding use of the FMO Service, like the number of users and frequency and manner of usage of the FMO Service. We may also collect aggregated information regarding the use of our subscription-based service network, such as the extent to which certain features are used. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of our user base, advertising use, customer patterns and related site information. We use this information to better understand how the FMO Service is used, and to improve the online experience of our users. This information is not used in a way that will personally identify you. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by FMO and our third-party advertising providers (such as Google Adsense) during the course of serving advertisements to our website (but not your name, address, or other personal information). Such information is used by FMO and our advertising providers to facilitate and monitor the serving of advertisements.

Similarly, we may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on our website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that our website places onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies identify your computer hard drive so that we can recognize you the next time you visit us. We use cookies to collect and store some information about you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website. We use this information to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. In the same manner, we may also engage third parties to monitor the usage of, and serve advertising to, the FMO Service. These third parties may use cookies to collect such information. You may disable cookies by following directions on your web browser. Disabling cookies also disables web beacons. You should be aware, however, that by disabling cookies you may be unable to access certain services and features of the FMO Service.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We may collect personally identifiable information from you when you seek access to certain portions of the FMO Service, or publish content, and/or register for our services. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, physical and e-mail addresses, phone and/or fax numbers, Internet address, type of computer as well as your preferences and usage patterns. This information may be used to fulfill your requests for services, to communicate with you about your account, to support your online activities, to respond to your questions, to customize your experience and to customize the content or features of the FMO Service. We may use your personally identifiable information to notify you of changes to the FMO Service, Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy. We may also use your personally identifiable information to personalize your interactive experience on the FMO Service. For example, if you have given us permission, we may use your information to inform you of other products or services that you may find valuable. We may also use the information you provide to make improvements that better serve our users' needs.

  * If you prefer not to receive information about additional products and services that we think you may be interested in, you can choose not to receive this information by opting-out when given the opportunity at the point we ask you for your contact information.

**Security**

FMO is committed to taking appropriate measures to protect your privacy against unauthorized disclosures. FMO uses a variety of secure techniques designed to protect your information.

While we have implemented safeguards, you should be aware that Internet security technology rapidly changes. As such, we cannot guarantee that the safeguards we employ today can protect your personal information from the threats of tomorrow, or that our security measures are failsafe and not subject to circumvention or unauthorized intrusion. You should also be aware that, despite our best efforts, factors beyond our control may result in disclosure of data.

**Third-Party Links**

Portions of the FMO Service may contain links to other third party websites that you may access. These other sites have their own privacy policies, and you should review those policies before following those links. We cannot control the information disclosed at these third-party sites or how that information is used.

**Young Children**

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. To best protect your child's privacy, we suggest that you carefully supervise your child's access to the Internet and our website.

**Opt-Out**

The FMO Service provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us regarding products and services in which you may be interested. You will be given this opportunity at the time we request information about you. If you do not opt-out at the time you provide information, but choose to opt-out later, use the link provided in any message.

**By using the FMO Service, you agree to the level of privacy protection set out in our Privacy Policy.**
